<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<langConfig xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" active = "false">
    
    <!-- This default section will be used if not explicitly defined in this document. -->
	<language val="default">
        <shortDesc>This is the short description used as default.</shortDesc>
	    <longDesc>This is the long description used as default.</longDesc>
        <iconImage>This is the url of the icon image that is used as default.</iconImage>
        <friendlyName>This is the name shown for the app that is used as default.</friendlyName>
    </language>
    
    <!-- When val equals "en" or any value before the "-" in the ISO locale standards, 
        it will be the default used for the entire en (english) locale if not explicitly 
        defined in this document. -->
    <language val="en">
        <shortDesc>This is the short description for the app in English</shortDesc>
        <longDesc>This is the long description for the app in English</longDesc>
        <iconImage>This is the url of the icon image that is used for English</iconImage>
        <friendlyName>This is the name shown for the app that is used for English</friendlyName>
    </language>
    
    <!-- The following are examples of explicit definitions. -->
    <language val="es-US">
        <shortDesc>This is the short description for the app in Español - United States</shortDesc>
        <iconImage>This is the url of the icon image that is used for Español - United States</iconImage>
        <friendlyName>This is the name shown for the app that is used for Español - United States</friendlyName>
    </language>
    <language val="es-ES">
        <shortDesc>This is the short description for the app in Español - Spain</shortDesc>
        <longDesc>This is the long description for the app in Español - Spain</longDesc>
        <friendlyName>This is the name shown for the app that is used for Español - Spain</friendlyName>
    </language>
    <language val="fr-CA">
        <shortDesc>This is the short description for the app in French - Canada</shortDesc>
        <longDesc>This is the long description for the app in French - Canada</longDesc>
        <iconImage>This is the url of the icon image that is used for French - Canada</iconImage>
        <friendlyName>This is the name shown for the app that is used for French - Canada</friendlyName>
    </language>
    <language val="fr-FR">
        <shortDesc>This is the short description for the app in French - France</shortDesc>
        <longDesc>This is the long description for the app in French - France</longDesc>
        <iconImage>This is the url of the icon image that is used for French - France</iconImage>
    </language>
</langConfig>
